[
    {
        "question":"What does TCS stand for?", 
        "ans1":"Tata Consultancy Services", 
        "ans2":"Technology Consultancy Services",
        "ans3":"Tata Computer Services",
        "ans4":"Technology Connections Services",
        "correct":"1"
    },
    {
        "question":"What does PC stand for?", 
        "ans1":"Professional Computer", 
        "ans2":"Performing Calculations",
        "ans3":"Personal Computer",
        "ans4":"Performance Completed",
        "correct":"3"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is 5+5?", 
        "ans1":"9", 
        "ans2":"10",
        "ans3":"11",
        "ans4":"12",
        "correct":"2"
    },
    {
        "question":"How many questions are on this exam?", 
        "ans1":"5", 
        "ans2":"10",
        "ans3":"15",
        "ans4":"20",
        "correct":"3"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is worn on the face?", 
        "ans1":"Pants", 
        "ans2":"Shoes",
        "ans3":"Shirt",
        "ans4":"Glasses",
        "correct":"4"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which country is the car company Kia from?", 
        "ans1":"United States of America", 
        "ans2":"South Korea",
        "ans3":"Japan",
        "ans4":"United Kingdom",
        "correct":"2"
    },
    {
        "question":"How many bits are in a byte?", 
        "ans1":"2", 
        "ans2":"4",
        "ans3":"8",
        "ans4":"16",
        "correct":"3"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which Phase End Project is this?", 
        "ans1":"Phase 1", 
        "ans2":"Phase 2",
        "ans3":"Phase 3",
        "ans4":"Phase 4",
        "correct":"2"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of these is not a Microsoft Office product?", 
        "ans1":"Word", 
        "ans2":"Excel",
        "ans3":"Outlook",
        "ans4":"Acrobat",
        "correct":"4"
    },
    {
        "question":"The virtual reality headset manufacturer Oculus is owned by which company?", 
        "ans1":"Google", 
        "ans2":"Apple",
        "ans3":"Microsoft",
        "ans4":"Facebook",
        "correct":"4"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of these is the JSON escape character?", 
        "ans1":"\\", 
        "ans2":"/",
        "ans3":"#",
        "ans4":"|",
        "correct":"1"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of these is an amphibian?", 
        "ans1":"Snake", 
        "ans2":"Turtle",
        "ans3":"Frog",
        "ans4":"Lizard",
        "correct":"3"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of these letters comes earliest in the alphabet?", 
        "ans1":"G", 
        "ans2":"C",
        "ans3":"E",
        "ans4":"H",
        "correct":"2"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is a dairy product?", 
        "ans1":"Milk", 
        "ans2":"Cheese",
        "ans3":"Yogurt",
        "ans4":"All of the above",
        "correct":"4"
    },
    {
        "question":"Are these good test questions?", 
        "ans1":"Absolutely!", 
        "ans2":"Probably",
        "ans3":"Most of them are",
        "ans4":"Definitely not",
        "correct":"4"
    }
]